id,content,named_entities,channel
1016267,"NOT 1 PERSON DIED FROM COVID EVER  COVID WAS NEVER ISOLATED  THE COMMON COLD, FLU ALONG WITH 5G WAS THE CAUSE OF HEALTH CONDITIONS    ASYMPTOMATIC WENT FOR TEST SWABS THAT INFECTED THEM WITH SYMPTOMS  FORCED DEATHS BY VENTILATORS  APPROXIMATELY 45-65k DIE EVERY YEAR FROM THE FLU  THOSE WITH PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS AND THE ELDERLY CAN DIE FROM THE FLU  NORMAL COLD SYMPTOMS AND THE FU WAS REBRANDED AND REMARKETING AS COVID 19  LAB LEAK: THERE ISN'T A VIRUS THAT WAS LEAKED THERE WAS: THE LEAK OF INFORMATION THE TAINTED SWABS THE VACCINE CREATED YEARS AGO  THE VACCINATED ARE BECOMING THE VIRUS","[{u'text': u'1', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'CONDITIONS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'45-65k', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'VIRUS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'LEAKED', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'TAINTED', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'YEARS AGO', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'VIRUS', u'type': u'ORG'}]",690
1022796,"The phone industry (Apple, at least) is starting to move everything to 5G. If you want a cell phone that isn't 5G, better grab it soon.  https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/apple-going-all-5g-its-2022-iphone-refresh","[{u'text': u'Apple', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",689
1029629,Someone please explain the 5G,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",701
1049454,"I keep adding to this with my notes since last year  The  FLU HAS ALWAYS BEEN FROM FREQUENCIES  NOT 1 PERSON DIED FROM COVID EVER  COVID WAS NEVER ISOLATED  THE COMMON COLD, FLU ALONG WITH 5G WAS THE CAUSE OF HEALTH CONDITIONS    ASYMPTOMATIC WENT FOR TEST SWABS THAT INFECTED THEM WITH SYMPTOMS  FORCED DEATHS BY VENTILATORS  APPROXIMATELY 45-65k DIE EVERY YEAR FROM THE FLU  THOSE WITH PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS AND THE ELDERLY CAN DIE FROM THE FLU  NORMAL COLD SYMPTOMS AND THE FU WAS REBRANDED AND REMARKETING AS COVID 19  LAB LEAK: THERE ISN'T A VIRUS THAT WAS LEAKED THERE WAS: THE LEAK OF INFORMATION THE TAINTED SWABS INFECTED YOU WITH A VIRUS (FLU) THE VACCINE CREATED YEARS AGO  THE VACCINATED ARE BECOMING THE VIRUS   It is from 5G - Radiation from the cells. There isn't a leak from Wuhan.  It's a cover-up   3 Pandemics in the last 120 Years  In 1918 - They implemented radio waves globally and increased the electrification of our universe causing the Spanish Flu - Most deaths during WW1   WW2 implantation of Radar by Rolling out Satellites - Van Allen belt  - Flu Pandemic  1968 Hong Kong Flu -  Rolled out another level of 100,000 satellites in the Transmitting Radar signals pushing telecommications again in the Van Allen Belt   5G - Takes about 6 months after exposure - If you were born into the Frequency World , You will not be affected. The youngest were born into this. They are covering their tracks as the continue to roll out towers. - Ends Results - Flu again and we are in a Digital Sensored WW3  They are pushing AI Technology now - Driverless cars run off 5G, Everything runs off 5G  RUSSIA - NO 5G Rollout - Look at the difference with Russia   Who else sees the patterns here?   Frequencies - Flu - War","[{u'text': u'last year', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'1', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'CONDITIONS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'45-65k', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'VIRUS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'LEAKED', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'VIRUS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'FLU', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'YEARS AGO', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'VIRUS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Wuhan', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'3', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'the last 120 Years', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'1918', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Spanish', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'Radar', u'type': u'PRODUCT'}, {u'text': u'1968', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Hong Kong', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'100,000', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Transmitting Radar', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'G - Takes', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'about 6 months', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'AI Technology', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Russia', u'type': u'GPE'}]",690
1050910,The FLU HAS ALWAYS BEEN FROM FREQUENCIES - Welcome To 5G https://rumble.com/vkcbsb-the-flu-has-always-been-from-frequencies-welcome-to-5g.html,"[{u'text': u'FLU', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",690
1096265,"I will be turning off my 5G and wifi on August 11th.  The Emergency Broadcast from FEMA is also a 5G test where the towers Haven't been turned on.  They  already affect the Unvaccinated   I know enough with frequencies, what they can do, expeciallly with Graphine Oxide and nano Particles with the jabbed  We all have seen enough videos to know what this will do  I will be back on shortly after  The group will still be open. ALWAYS!   https://www.fcc.gov/document/fema-and-fcc-plan-nationwide-emergency-alert-test-aug-11","[{u'text': u'August 11th', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'The Emergency Broadcast', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'FEMA', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'the Unvaccinated nn', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Graphine Oxide', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'ALWAYS', u'type': u'ORG'}]",690
1107592,Trying to a better picture  But this is 5G - Induction of coronavirus through skin cells  Frequency radiation - A 5G coverup  August 11th they are switching on 5G  God help us all with the jabbed  Even the unvaccinated are affected by 5G,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'August 11th', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",690
1115609,"READY FOR THE 5G AND COVID HOTSPOT MAPS OF 2020 THAT OVERLAP ALMOST EXACTLY!  North east coast / Canada Border, Florida, Washington, Texas, and California are Exact  It's a 5G coverup.There isn't a virus. Its Radiation from the skin Cells  THIS IS WHAT I HAVE EXPLAINED SINCE LAST YEAR","[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'2020', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'North east coast', u'type': u'LOC'}, {u'text': u'Florida', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Washington', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Texas', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'California', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'EXPLAINED', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'LAST YEAR', u'type': u'DATE'}]",690
1115673,Candace Owen pointing out 5G. Important topic. Share everything you know about 5G and 5G towers 👇 SHARING IS CARING  =================== 🍿Channel @TRUMPINTEL  🍿 Chat @AwakeningGlobal,"[{u'text': u'Candace Owen', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'U0001f37fChannel', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'@TRUMPINTEL', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f37f', u'type': u'DATE'}]",701
1127131,I highly recommend that no one gets on a flight during August 11th or anytime soon  The EBS is also turning on the unused 5G towers  Jabbed - Graphine Oxide - Nano Particles   Blood clots,"[{u'text': u'August 11th', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'EBS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",690
1352055,"[Inoltrato da ☯️ Manuela Pat 🇮🇹 🇺🇸 Sil 🇮🇹 VOICES OF ITALY 🇮🇹 - CHANNEL (Manuela Pat 🇮🇹 🇺🇸)] IMPORTANT FINDINGS about GUSTAVO ROL ————————————————————————————- “I discovered a tremendous law that binds the green color, the musical fifth and heat. I have lost the joy of living. Power scares me "" GUSTAVO ROL 🌍🌎🌏 BINGO !!! and he had seen it !! that's why he lost the will to live !! ""Green"" transition, 5G (electromagnetic vibrations with consequent heat like the microwave), in the Anglo-Saxon musical notation the note 🎼  G is the SOL in the Europe version of music scale/language and it is exactly the fifth of C (DO) ....😱😱😱😱 https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gustavo_Rol","[{u'text': u'Inoltrato da u262f', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Manuela Pat U0001f1eeU0001f1f9 U0001f1fa', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'U0001f1f8', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Sil U0001f1ee', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f1f9 - CHANNEL', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Manuela Pat U0001f1eeU0001f1f9 U0001f1fa', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'U0001f1f8', u'type': u'PRODUCT'}, {u'text': u'GUSTAVO ROLn', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'fifth', u'type': u'ORDINAL'}, {u'text': u'GUSTAVO ROL', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f30e', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Anglo', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'U0001f3bc  G', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Europe', u'type': u'LOC'}, {u'text': u'fifth', u'type': u'ORDINAL'}, {u'text': u'U0001f631', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'U0001f631', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f631', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f631', u'type': u'ORG'}]",395
1359735,There are messing up the 5G connection here,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",690
1366858,"Breaking news: Patrick King proves in Court that the Covid is fake, a fake virus invented by the vaccine companies to sell a fake cure. We know this. Now, lets make this video viral. Follow our channel for more info: https://t.me/covidvaccineexemption Protect yourself from 5G frequencies with Aulterra more info on this page:  https://dq271.isrefer.com/go/AultHome/AUL651/","[{u'text': u'Patrick King', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Court', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Covid', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Aulterra', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'https://dq271.isrefer.com/go/AultHome/AUL651/', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",395
1369186,"starlink isn't enough, now we need military grade 5G blasting the earth as well... https://www.congress.gov/bill/117th-congress/house-bill/5123/text","[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'https://www.congress.gov/bill/117th-congress/house-bill/5123/text', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",690
1369234,The 5G Towers Have To Come Down - This is why people Believe there is a Pandemic and are getting the jab   Covid is a 5G COVER-UP!   https://rumble.com/vm8r4p-5g-big-data-revolution-artificial-intelligence.html,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Believe', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Covid', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'https://rumble.com/vm8r4p-5g-big-data-revolution-artificial-intelligence.html', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",690
1369437,💥💥💥💥  CALL TO ACTION  SHARE EVERYWHERE AND  SIGN HERE PLEASE - STOP THE 5G!  Action Alert: Time to Put Our Historic Win on 5G and Wireless Harm Into Action!   https://childrenshealthdefense.org/action/chds-historic-win-action-alert/,"[{u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Wireless Harm', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'https://childrenshealthdefense.org/action/chds-historic-win-action-alert/', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",690
1371188,"This is a MUST READ: Official French Army Report on C19 and 5G. If this doesn't wake you up, NOTHING will!","[{u'text': u'C19', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'NOTHING', u'type': u'ORG'}]",395
1377121,All related to 5G - Frequencies,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'G - Frequencies', u'type': u'ORG'}]",690
1382789,💥💥💥💥  PLEASE SIGN HERE IF YOU HAVEN'T YET -   STOP THE 5G! THIS IS WHAT COVID IS  Action Alert: Time to Put Our Historic Win on 5G and Wireless Harm Into Action!   https://childrenshealthdefense.org/action/chds-historic-win-action-alert/,"[{u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5nnPLEASE SIGN HERE IF', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Wireless Harm', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'https://childrenshealthdefense.org/action/chds-historic-win-action-alert/', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",690
1384620,The shots have Graphine Oxide which can interact with 5G.  My 3G phone is being discontinued in Jan.  Have to go to 5G or no phone. How convenient for them.  They are put this poison in everything.  In UK they approved it to us in water supply.  Its sprayed in the air through Chemtrails.   Its causing all kinds of problem in the body.. Do the research.,"[{u'text': u'Graphine Oxide', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5G.', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Jan.', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'UK', u'type': u'GPE'}]",395
1386105,Stop the 5G  We don't even have any words.  What this woman did was absolutely unspeakable.  https://www.lawenforcementtoday.com/miami-mom-accused-of-drowning-15-month-old-toddler-stabbing-husband/   @CallingASpadeASpade ♠️,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'@CallingASpadeASpade u2660ufe0f', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",690
1400525,Extremely high radiation being emitted from 5G tower. @HATSTRUTH 🎩,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'@HATSTRUTH', u'type': u'ORG'}]",119
1401653,They're Still not getting that's 5G - That's why they can't isolate it. Radiation to the skin cells  CCP TOWERS  NEW - 26 out of the 27 Lancet scientists who trashed theory that Covid leaked from a Chinese lab have links to Wuhan researchers.  https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9980015/26-Lancet-scientists-trashed-theory-Covid-leaked-Chinese-lab-links-Wuhan.html  @disclosetv,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'CCP', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'26', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'27', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Lancet', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Covid', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'Wuhan', u'type': u'GPE'}]",690
1408920,The Cause of COVID Deaths No One Wants to Talk About - 5G  https://childrenshealthdefense.org/defender/pandemic-cause-toxic-exposure/,"[{u'text': u'The Cause of COVID Deaths No One Wants', u'type': u'ORG'}]",690
1419079,Graphine Oxide + Nano Particles + 5G = Behavioral Control  Now what will happen when DS sets off a signal??  What army are they making?,"[{u'text': u'Graphine Oxide + Nano Particles', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Behavioral Control', u'type': u'ORG'}]",690
1427378,"It won't be a chip. It will be the nanoparticles injected into the body, with these experimental gene therapy shots everyone has been getting... Not only does it alter the genetics, but it will also begin influencing the minds of the recipients, as well. This is essentially why 5G wireless networks were quietly rolled out, worldwide, during the lockdowns. Their system can't function without it. The science is called ""magneto-genetics""..and no one is ready for what's to come from it.","[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'magneto-genetics""', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}]",395
1438548,"REPOSTING    I keep adding to this with my notes since last year  The  FLU HAS ALWAYS BEEN FROM FREQUENCIES  NOT 1 PERSON DIED FROM COVID EVER  COVID WAS NEVER ISOLATED  THE COMMON COLD, FLU ALONG WITH 5G WAS THE CAUSE OF HEALTH CONDITIONS    ASYMPTOMATIC WENT FOR TEST SWABS THAT INFECTED THEM WITH SYMPTOMS  FORCED DEATHS BY VENTILATORS  APPROXIMATELY 45-65k DIE EVERY YEAR FROM THE FLU  THOSE WITH PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS AND THE ELDERLY CAN DIE FROM THE FLU  NORMAL COLD SYMPTOMS AND THE FU WAS REBRANDED AND REMARKETING AS COVID 19  LAB LEAK: THERE ISN'T A VIRUS THAT WAS LEAKED THERE WAS: THE LEAK OF INFORMATION THE TAINTED SWABS INFECTED YOU WITH A VIRUS (FLU) THE VACCINE CREATED YEARS AGO  THE VACCINATED ARE BECOMING THE VIRUS   It is from 5G - Radiation from the cells. There isn't a leak from Wuhan.  It's a cover-up   3 Pandemics in the last 120 Years  In 1918 - They implemented radio waves globally and increased the electrification of our universe causing the Spanish Flu - Most deaths during WW1   WW2 implantation of Radar by Rolling out Satellites - Van Allen belt  - Flu Pandemic  1968 Hong Kong Flu -  Rolled out another level of 100,000 satellites in the Transmitting Radar signals pushing telecommications again in the Van Allen Belt   5G - Takes about 6 months after exposure - If you were born with Frequencies , You are mostly likely not affected. The youngest were born into this. They are covering their tracks as the continue to roll out towers. - Ends Results - Flu again and we are in WW3  They are pushing AI Technology now - Driverless cars run off 5G, Everything runs off 5G  Who else sees the patterns here?   Frequencies - Flu - War  THE FLU HAS ALWAYS BEEN A FREQUENCY COVER-UP  COVID IS A 5G COVER-UP","[{u'text': u'last year', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'1', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'CONDITIONS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'45-65k', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'VIRUS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'LEAKED', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'VIRUS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'FLU', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'YEARS AGO', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'VIRUS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Wuhan', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'3', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'the last 120 Years', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'1918', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Spanish', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'Radar', u'type': u'PRODUCT'}, {u'text': u'1968', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Hong Kong', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'100,000', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Transmitting Radar', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'G - Takes', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'about 6 months', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'AI Technology', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'FLU', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",690
1438607,💥💥💥💥  PLEASE SIGN HERE IF YOU HAVEN'T YET -   STOP THE 5G! THIS IS WHAT COVID IS  Action Alert: Time to Put This Historic Win on 5G and Wireless Harm Into Action!   https://childrenshealthdefense.org/action/chds-historic-win-action-alert/,"[{u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5nnPLEASE SIGN HERE IF', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Wireless Harm', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'https://childrenshealthdefense.org/action/chds-historic-win-action-alert/', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",690
1438634,Remember Trump Stated He Wanted To Take Out The CCP 5G Towers,[],690
1438715,Fauci's NIH Study Reveals 5G Technology Can Produce Coronavirus In Human Cells » Sons of Liberty Media https://sonsoflibertymedia.com/faucis-nih-study-reveals-5g-tecnology-can-produce-coronavirus-in-human-cells/,"[{u'text': u'Fauci', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'NIH Study Reveals', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Liberty Media', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'https://sonsoflibertymedia.com/faucis-nih-study-reveals-5g-tecnology-can-produce-coronavirus-in-human-cells/', u'type': u'ORG'}]",690
1447713,"IMPORTANT FINDINGS about GUSTAVO ROL ——————————————————————— “I discovered a tremendous law that binds the green color, the musical scale 5th and heat. I have lost the joy of living. Power scares me "" GUSTAVO ROL 🌍🌎🌏 BINGO !!! and he had seen it !! that's why he lost the will to live !! ""Green"" transition, 5G (electromagnetic vibrations with consequent heat like the microwave), in the Anglo-Saxon musical notation the note 🎼  G is the SOL in the Europe version of music scale/language and it is exactly the fifth of C (DO) ....😱😱😱😱 https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gustavo_Rol","[{u'text': u'GUSTAVO ROLn', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5th', u'type': u'ORDINAL'}, {u'text': u'GUSTAVO ROL', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f30e', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Anglo', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'U0001f3bc  G', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Europe', u'type': u'LOC'}, {u'text': u'fifth', u'type': u'ORDINAL'}, {u'text': u'U0001f631', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'U0001f631', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f631', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f631', u'type': u'ORG'}]",395
1454188,STOP THE 5G  THIS IS A COVER-UP,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",690
1461278,"STARTING WITH JUST A REMINDER  *THEN LATER I WILL FINISH 5G WITH HOW WE CAN PROTECT OURSELVES*  BLACK VS WHITE BAPTIST VS CATHOLIC GAY VS STRAIGHT MASKED VS UNMASKED VAXX’ed VS UNVAXX’ed  YOU SEE WHERE I AM GOING!  IN THE LAST TWO DAYS I HAVE SEEN NOTHING BUT A FLOOD/PUSH OF  THE NEXT TOOL OF DIVISION!  EVEN WITH SOME I HAVE TRUSTED!  MAYBE IT IS BY ACCIDENT; MAYBE THEY THINK THE UNVAXX’ed HAVE PERSECUTION COMING?  I DO NOT KNOW THE MOTIVE, BUT I KNOW THE OUTCOME; DIVISION!  SOME OTHER TOOL TO DIVIDE AND CONQUER!   👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼 “THE UNVAXX’ed ARE BEING BLAMED FOR THE DEATHS OF THE VAXX’ed”!   DO NOT FALL FOR IT!  STAY FOCUSED ON “TOGETHER WE ARE STRONG”!  “DIVIDED WE WILL FALL!” THINK OF THE TIMING!  BIG CELEB COMES OUT AGAINST CENSORSHIP; WAKING MORE UP; JOINING MORE FORCES; BAM!  HERE COMES THE DIVISION PUSH!   CIVIL WAR ON ANY FRONT REVEALS THE GUNS; and STUPIDITY OF THOSE RUFFLED WILL DIE IN THE STREETS!   DO NOT LET THEM DIVIDE US!  DO NOT FALL FOR THEIR SAME PLAYS!    AS A NURSE, RT, and/or a PATRIOT I WILL CARE FOR SOMEONE NO MATTER WHAT!  VAXX, NO VAXX, BLACK, WHITE, BAPTIST, ATHEIST, GAY OR STRAIGHT!  DEM OR REP!   I DO NOT CHOOSE IN AN EMERGENCY WHO I WILL, and WILL NOT CARE FOR!  LIFE AND LIMB COME FIRST!  WHO, WHAT, PAST OR PRESENT MATTER NOT TO ME, and I HAVE NEVER ASKED!  I WOULD NOT ASK EVER!  IT DOES NOT MATTER!!  NOT BEFORE I CARE FOR THEM OR AFTER!  ALL THAT MATTERS IN THAT MOMENT; IN THAT EMERGENCY; IS THE LIFE GOD HAS PLACED BEFORE ME!  IT IS A PRECIOUS LIFE CHERISHED BY THAT PERSON, and THOSE WHO LOVE THAT PERSON!  NOTHING SUPERFICIALLY HAS OR EVER WILL STOP ME FROM GIVING ALL OF MYSELF IN THAT EMERGENCY NO MATTER WHAT!  WHAT WOULD YOU DO? WHAT WOULD YOU WANT FOR YOU OR YOUR LOVED ONE?  ARE WE NOT IN AN EMERGENCY?  I NEVER HAVE WORKED AN EMERGENCY AS AN ER NURSE OR RT ALONE; IT ALWAYS HAS REQUIRED A “TEAM”!  ~CRISSY~","[{u'text': u'ACCIDENT', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'THE UNVAXXu2019ed ARE BEING BLAMED FOR THE DEATHS OF THE', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'STREETS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'US', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'AS A', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'NURSE', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'RT', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'VAXX', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'NO VAXX', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'BLACK', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'WHITE', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'BAPTIST', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'ATHEIST', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'GAY OR', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'NEVER', u'type': u'ORG'}]",395
1462137,"👆👆👆👆👆👆 From the governor/president of the ABRUZZO region in Italy 🇮🇹 💥💥💥💥💥💥💥💥💥💥💥 GREEN PASS: MY THOUGHT  I find an irrevocable contradiction between the 'moral suasion' invoked to preserve the optional nature of the vaccine and the restrictions with related sanctions imposed on those who do not (including the suspension of salary and contributions).  'Persuasion' is another thing, and it is done (as also invoked by President Zaia) with powerful, clear and effective information campaigns capable of resolving doubts and perplexities.  Of course, no one will ever convince the paranoid who think that graphite or other substances that can be activated with the 5G antennas are injected with the vaccine to control consciences ... but that is a marginal world and not very significant numerically.  But the many who are in the gray area of ​​confusion or uncertainty, those can be 'recovered' and convinced.  Instead, we are choosing to do everything we can not to impose the obligation for fear of the 'conflict' it would generate, but I fear that the conflict that is being created with this choice could be even worse.  It would be more honest, linear and less conflictual to impose the obligation, resulting in the assumption of compensation liability in the event of serious side effects (rare but unfortunately existing).  Obligation that today applies to a series of vaccines related to diseases that are currently much less dangerous and present than Covid.  Not making the choice of obligation but 'forcing' those who do not want to get the vaccine making their life impossible feeds the legitimate suspicion that the State does not want to impose the obligation in order not to pay any compensation.  And this argument cannot fail to feed suspicion and uncertainty in a non-marginal part of the population.","[{u'text': u'Italy', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'U0001f1ee', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f1f9', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4a5', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Zaia', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'today', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Covid', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'State', u'type': u'ORG'}]",395
1465952,Rename your WiFi to Covid 19 5G test tower. Make the life of your neighbor brighter and exciting,"[{u'text': u'WiFi', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",690
1498395,"WARNING: PHONES AND LAPTOPS HAVE BEEN UPDATED TO EMIT RADIATION THAT SIMULATES COVID SYMPTOMS... FATIGUE ETC, ADD THICK FOIL TO YOUR PHONES AND LAPTOPS. VARY THE PATTERNS.  Covid is 5G!  They are hitting Patriots more than ever","[{u'text': u'PHONES', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'ETC', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Covid', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Patriots', u'type': u'ORG'}]",690
1499783,I’ve been traveling a lot. I’ve been feeling this myself. Call me crazy or whatever. My body tells me when I’m around unsafe things now. From 5G to the vaxed. My ears ring. I can feel pressure and other things. My friend Gary can smell it. Anyone else experiencing this?,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Gary', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",395
3598117,"📺 Interview With Ren Zhengfei, Founder And CEO Of Chinese Telecom Giant Huawei  Ren Zhengfei, founder and CEO of Chinese telecom giant Huawei, spoke to Time on U.S. actions against his company, the security of Huawei's product, his daughter and Huawei CFO's arrest, President Donald Trump and 5G technology.  📺 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nl2jCWDwE8w  #china #huawei #founder #interview #video #podcast 📡@cRyPtHoN_INFOSEC_DE 📡@cRyPtHoN_INFOSEC_EN 📡@cRyPtHoN_INFOSEC_ES 📡@FLOSSb0xIN","[{u'text': u'Chinese Telecom Giant Huawei', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'Huawei', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Time', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U.S.', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Huawei', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u""Huawei CFO's"", u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Donald Trump', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'#china #', u'type': u'MONEY'}, {u'text': u'#founder #', u'type': u'MONEY'}, {u'text': u'#', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4e1', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4e1', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4e1@cRyPtHoN_INFOSEC_ES', u'type': u'PERCENT'}, {u'text': u'U0001f4e1', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",14859
3599627,⚠️Bund will 5G Antennen auf KINDERGÄRTEN und SCHULEN ❗️  👍Auch als VIDEO abrufbar⤵️ t.me/buergerinformative/2355  Quelle: @Odysseus108 YT-ID: 9o7Nqobai3w ——————————————- #Podcast #Odysseus t.me/b_info_audio/48,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'SCHULEN u2757', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Quelle', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'@Odysseus108nYT-ID', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'9o7Nqobai3w', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u't.me/b_info_audio/48', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}]",3782
3655953,⚠️Was hat der Corona-Virus mit 5G zu tun❓  👇Zu BÜRGERINFORMATIVE-News t.me/buergerinformative/5748  Quelle: @AkashaTV YT/invidio-ID: 8ZR_XrO2UGs ——————————————- #Politik #Coronavirus #China #Wuhan #5G #MMS #AkashaTV t.me/b_info_audio/2868,"[{u'text': u'Corona-Virus', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'8ZR_XrO2UGs', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'#China', u'type': u'MONEY'}]",3782
3655954,⚠️Was hat der Corona-Virus mit 5G zu tun❓  👇Zu BÜRGERINFORMATIVE-News t.me/buergerinformative/5748  Quelle: @AkashaTV YT/invidio-ID: 8ZR_XrO2UGs ——————————————- #Politik #Coronavirus #China #Wuhan #5G #MMS #AkashaTV t.me/b_info_audio/2869,"[{u'text': u'Corona-Virus', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'8ZR_XrO2UGs', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'#China', u'type': u'MONEY'}]",3782
4119645,"Corona Virus is the 5G, symbolism on the new 20 pound note, conspiracy theorists have been RIGHT once again   5g und Coronavirussymbol abgebildet.   Bitte verteilen !!!! @freeyourmindkanal  Mehr Informationen hier", 275125,14859
6514286,Beyond the Memo Infographic  https://throughthelookingglassnews.files.wordpress.com/2017/11/final_memo_epochtimes-1-e1517754294263.jpg Space Race Infographic  https://www.theepochtimes.com/assets/uploads/2018/03/22/The_New_Space_Race_Epoch_Times-1.jpg Hilary Clinton - Insurance Policy Infographic  https://throughthelookingglassnews.files.wordpress.com/2017/11/fusion-gps-map_the-epoch-times.jpg JFK & MLK - Assassination Committee decides not to investigate  https://www.archives.gov/files/research/jfk/releases/docid-32403785.pdf Uranium One Scandal Infographic  https://throughthelookingglassnews.files.wordpress.com/2017/11/epoch_times_uranium_one_final.jpg Unlawful Spying FISA Infographic  https://img.theepochtimes.com/assets/uploads/2018/03/22/fisa-spying-infographic.jpg China War on America Infographic  https://cdn.epoch.cloud/infographics/Chinas_Secret_War_Against_America_Epoch-Times_Infographic.pdf Coronavirus Zero Hedge  https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/coronavirus-contains-hiv-insertions-stoking-fears-over-artificially-created-bioweapon Soros Ran American Organizations  http://www.ruthfullyyours.com/2010/11/16/read-this-mind-boggling-list-of-soros-funded-organizations/ Just The News John Solomon - Russia Collusion Hoax  https://justthenews.com/accountability/political-ethics/key-witness-told-team-mueller-russia-collusion-evidence-found Mockingbird Media  https://centipedenation.com/analysis-and-reports/operation-mockingbird-a-social-engineered-reality/ Declass - POTUS Oval Address China Coronavirus  https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/11/politics/read-trump-coronavirus-address/index.html 5G Tracking Map  https://www.speedtest.net/ookla-5g-map Fake News Exposed  https://docs.google.com/document/d/1mbZgeLkbnkXdZPf9pFlivaqHrMibqSQR8IgCEXtDtSg/edit Declass FISA docs new 4/16/20  https://www.judiciary.senate.gov/fisa-investigation Declass - DHS Biodefense Lab Study  https://www.scribd.com/document/456897616/DHSST Declass - Flynn: Second Supplement to Motion to Dismiss  https://www.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.dcd.191592/gov.uscourts.dcd.191592.189.0_1.pdf FISA Abuse Timeline: Epoch  https://cdn.epoch.cloud/assets/static_assets/FISA-abuse-timeline.jpg Declass - Planned Parenthood officials admit under oath to selling aborted body parts  https://www.liveaction.org/news/bombshell-planned-parenthood-admits-oath-aborted-parts/ Declass - Massive Dump of Video Clips Documentation Looters and Violent Riots During George Floyd Protests  https://centipedenation.com/transmissions/massive-dump-of-video-clips-documenting-looters-and-violent-riots-during-george-floyd-protests/ Eric Trump Posted Q WWG1WGA Meme Archived Link  https://archive.is/2Lay7 How the Chinese Regime Colluded with WHO During the Pandemic  https://e.infogram.com/d1919ad0-53e5-45a5-88c3-44ba8b23af19?parent_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theepochtimes.com%2Finfographic-how-the-chinese-regime-colluded-with-who-during-the-pandemic_3372694.html&src=embed#async_embed Declass - Resignation List  https://www.resignation.info/list Declass Pizzagate Links / Archives  https://archive.is/BRC09 Declass - Flynn: Exculpatory Evidence Unsealed - Priestap Notes  https://justthenews.com/sites/default/files/2020-04/FlynnFBINotes_0.pdf Declass - Flynn: Exculpatory Evidence Unsealed - Filing  https://www.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.dcd.191592/gov.uscourts.dcd.191592.189.0_1.pdf Declass 53 HPSCI Transcripts (Russia Investigation Testimonies)  https://www.dni.gov/index.php/features/2753-53-hpsci-transcripts Declass - Susan Rice E-mail Targeting Michael Flynn  https://www.scribd.com/document/462170596/Declassified-Susan-Rice-E-Mail-Targeting-Michael-Flynn Declass - List of Unmaskings  https://www.hsgac.senate.gov/imo/media/doc/2020-05-13%20ODNI%20to%20CEG%20RHJ%20(Unmasking).pdf Declass - FBI Document that Launched CrossFire Hurricane  https://www.judicialwatch.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/JW-v-DOJ-reply-02743.pdf Declass - General Flynn / Kislyak Transcripts  https://www.grassley.senate.gov/sites/default/files/2020-05-29%20ODNI%20to%20CEG%20RHJ%20%28Flynn%20Transcripts%29.pdf,"[{u'text': u'Hilary Clinton - Insurance', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'MLK - Assassination Committee', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'One', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'FISA Infographic', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'https://img.theepochtimes.com/assets/uploads/2018/03/22/fisa-spying-infographic.jpg', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'China War on America Infographic  ', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'Zero', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Just The News John Solomon - Russia Collusion Hoax  https://justthenews.com/accountability/political-ethics/key-witness-told-team-mueller-russia-collusion-evidence-foundnMockingbird Media  https://centipedenation.com/analysis-and-reports/operation-mockingbird-a-social-engineered-reality/', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'4/16/20', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'FISA Abuse Timeline: Epoch  https://cdn.epoch.cloud/assets/static_assets/FISA-abuse-timeline.jpgnDeclass - Planned Parenthood', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'George Floyd Protests  https://centipedenation.com/transmissions/massive-dump-of-video-clips-documenting-looters-and-violent-riots-during-george-floyd-protests/', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Eric Trump', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'53', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Susan Rice E', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Michael Flynn  ', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Flynn / Kislyak Transcripts', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",37
6514289,Beyond the Memo Infographic  https://throughthelookingglassnews.files.wordpress.com/2017/11/final_memo_epochtimes-1-e1517754294263.jpg Space Race Infographic  https://www.theepochtimes.com/assets/uploads/2018/03/22/The_New_Space_Race_Epoch_Times-1.jpg Hilary Clinton - Insurance Policy Infographic  https://throughthelookingglassnews.files.wordpress.com/2017/11/fusion-gps-map_the-epoch-times.jpg JFK & MLK - Assassination Committee decides not to investigate  https://www.archives.gov/files/research/jfk/releases/docid-32403785.pdf Uranium One Scandal Infographic  https://throughthelookingglassnews.files.wordpress.com/2017/11/epoch_times_uranium_one_final.jpg Unlawful Spying FISA Infographic  https://img.theepochtimes.com/assets/uploads/2018/03/22/fisa-spying-infographic.jpg China War on America Infographic  https://cdn.epoch.cloud/infographics/Chinas_Secret_War_Against_America_Epoch-Times_Infographic.pdf Coronavirus Zero Hedge  https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/coronavirus-contains-hiv-insertions-stoking-fears-over-artificially-created-bioweapon Soros Ran American Organizations  http://www.ruthfullyyours.com/2010/11/16/read-this-mind-boggling-list-of-soros-funded-organizations/ Just The News John Solomon - Russia Collusion Hoax  https://justthenews.com/accountability/political-ethics/key-witness-told-team-mueller-russia-collusion-evidence-found Mockingbird Media  https://centipedenation.com/analysis-and-reports/operation-mockingbird-a-social-engineered-reality/ Declass - POTUS Oval Address China Coronavirus  https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/11/politics/read-trump-coronavirus-address/index.html 5G Tracking Map  https://www.speedtest.net/ookla-5g-map Fake News Exposed  https://docs.google.com/document/d/1mbZgeLkbnkXdZPf9pFlivaqHrMibqSQR8IgCEXtDtSg/edit Declass FISA docs new 4/16/20  https://www.judiciary.senate.gov/fisa-investigation Declass - DHS Biodefense Lab Study  https://www.scribd.com/document/456897616/DHSST Declass - Flynn: Second Supplement to Motion to Dismiss  https://www.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.dcd.191592/gov.uscourts.dcd.191592.189.0_1.pdf FISA Abuse Timeline: Epoch  https://cdn.epoch.cloud/assets/static_assets/FISA-abuse-timeline.jpg Declass - Planned Parenthood officials admit under oath to selling aborted body parts  https://www.liveaction.org/news/bombshell-planned-parenthood-admits-oath-aborted-parts/ Declass - Massive Dump of Video Clips Documentation Looters and Violent Riots During George Floyd Protests  https://centipedenation.com/transmissions/massive-dump-of-video-clips-documenting-looters-and-violent-riots-during-george-floyd-protests/ Eric Trump Posted Q WWG1WGA Meme Archived Link  https://archive.is/2Lay7 How the Chinese Regime Colluded with WHO During the Pandemic  https://e.infogram.com/d1919ad0-53e5-45a5-88c3-44ba8b23af19?parent_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theepochtimes.com%2Finfographic-how-the-chinese-regime-colluded-with-who-during-the-pandemic_3372694.html&src=embed#async_embed Declass - Resignation List  https://www.resignation.info/list Declass Pizzagate Links / Archives  https://archive.is/BRC09 Declass - Flynn: Exculpatory Evidence Unsealed - Priestap Notes  https://justthenews.com/sites/default/files/2020-04/FlynnFBINotes_0.pdf Declass - Flynn: Exculpatory Evidence Unsealed - Filing  https://www.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.dcd.191592/gov.uscourts.dcd.191592.189.0_1.pdf Declass 53 HPSCI Transcripts (Russia Investigation Testimonies)  https://www.dni.gov/index.php/features/2753-53-hpsci-transcripts Declass - Susan Rice E-mail Targeting Michael Flynn  https://www.scribd.com/document/462170596/Declassified-Susan-Rice-E-Mail-Targeting-Michael-Flynn Declass - List of Unmaskings  https://www.hsgac.senate.gov/imo/media/doc/2020-05-13%20ODNI%20to%20CEG%20RHJ%20(Unmasking).pdf Declass - FBI Document that Launched CrossFire Hurricane  https://www.judicialwatch.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/JW-v-DOJ-reply-02743.pdf Declass - General Flynn / Kislyak Transcripts  https://www.grassley.senate.gov/sites/default/files/2020-05-29%20ODNI%20to%20CEG%20RHJ%20%28Flynn%20Transcripts%29.pdf,"[{u'text': u'Hilary Clinton - Insurance', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'MLK - Assassination Committee', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'One', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'FISA Infographic', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'https://img.theepochtimes.com/assets/uploads/2018/03/22/fisa-spying-infographic.jpg', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'China War on America Infographic  ', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'Zero', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Just The News John Solomon - Russia Collusion Hoax  https://justthenews.com/accountability/political-ethics/key-witness-told-team-mueller-russia-collusion-evidence-foundnMockingbird Media  https://centipedenation.com/analysis-and-reports/operation-mockingbird-a-social-engineered-reality/', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'4/16/20', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'FISA Abuse Timeline: Epoch  https://cdn.epoch.cloud/assets/static_assets/FISA-abuse-timeline.jpgnDeclass - Planned Parenthood', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'George Floyd Protests  https://centipedenation.com/transmissions/massive-dump-of-video-clips-documenting-looters-and-violent-riots-during-george-floyd-protests/', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Eric Trump', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'53', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Susan Rice E', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Michael Flynn  ', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Flynn / Kislyak Transcripts', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",37
6514290,Beyond the Memo Infographic  https://throughthelookingglassnews.files.wordpress.com/2017/11/final_memo_epochtimes-1-e1517754294263.jpg Space Race Infographic  https://www.theepochtimes.com/assets/uploads/2018/03/22/The_New_Space_Race_Epoch_Times-1.jpg Hilary Clinton - Insurance Policy Infographic  https://throughthelookingglassnews.files.wordpress.com/2017/11/fusion-gps-map_the-epoch-times.jpg JFK & MLK - Assassination Committee decides not to investigate  https://www.archives.gov/files/research/jfk/releases/docid-32403785.pdf Uranium One Scandal Infographic  https://throughthelookingglassnews.files.wordpress.com/2017/11/epoch_times_uranium_one_final.jpg Unlawful Spying FISA Infographic  https://img.theepochtimes.com/assets/uploads/2018/03/22/fisa-spying-infographic.jpg China War on America Infographic  https://cdn.epoch.cloud/infographics/Chinas_Secret_War_Against_America_Epoch-Times_Infographic.pdf Coronavirus Zero Hedge  https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/coronavirus-contains-hiv-insertions-stoking-fears-over-artificially-created-bioweapon Soros Ran American Organizations  http://www.ruthfullyyours.com/2010/11/16/read-this-mind-boggling-list-of-soros-funded-organizations/ Just The News John Solomon - Russia Collusion Hoax  https://justthenews.com/accountability/political-ethics/key-witness-told-team-mueller-russia-collusion-evidence-found Mockingbird Media  https://centipedenation.com/analysis-and-reports/operation-mockingbird-a-social-engineered-reality/ Declass - POTUS Oval Address China Coronavirus  https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/11/politics/read-trump-coronavirus-address/index.html 5G Tracking Map  https://www.speedtest.net/ookla-5g-map Fake News Exposed  https://docs.google.com/document/d/1mbZgeLkbnkXdZPf9pFlivaqHrMibqSQR8IgCEXtDtSg/edit Declass FISA docs new 4/16/20  https://www.judiciary.senate.gov/fisa-investigation Declass - DHS Biodefense Lab Study  https://www.scribd.com/document/456897616/DHSST Declass - Flynn: Second Supplement to Motion to Dismiss  https://www.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.dcd.191592/gov.uscourts.dcd.191592.189.0_1.pdf FISA Abuse Timeline: Epoch  https://cdn.epoch.cloud/assets/static_assets/FISA-abuse-timeline.jpg Declass - Planned Parenthood officials admit under oath to selling aborted body parts  https://www.liveaction.org/news/bombshell-planned-parenthood-admits-oath-aborted-parts/ Declass - Massive Dump of Video Clips Documentation Looters and Violent Riots During George Floyd Protests  https://centipedenation.com/transmissions/massive-dump-of-video-clips-documenting-looters-and-violent-riots-during-george-floyd-protests/ Eric Trump Posted Q WWG1WGA Meme Archived Link  https://archive.is/2Lay7 How the Chinese Regime Colluded with WHO During the Pandemic  https://e.infogram.com/d1919ad0-53e5-45a5-88c3-44ba8b23af19?parent_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theepochtimes.com%2Finfographic-how-the-chinese-regime-colluded-with-who-during-the-pandemic_3372694.html&src=embed#async_embed Declass - Resignation List  https://www.resignation.info/list Declass Pizzagate Links / Archives  https://archive.is/BRC09 Declass - Flynn: Exculpatory Evidence Unsealed - Priestap Notes  https://justthenews.com/sites/default/files/2020-04/FlynnFBINotes_0.pdf Declass - Flynn: Exculpatory Evidence Unsealed - Filing  https://www.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.dcd.191592/gov.uscourts.dcd.191592.189.0_1.pdf Declass 53 HPSCI Transcripts (Russia Investigation Testimonies)  https://www.dni.gov/index.php/features/2753-53-hpsci-transcripts Declass - Susan Rice E-mail Targeting Michael Flynn  https://www.scribd.com/document/462170596/Declassified-Susan-Rice-E-Mail-Targeting-Michael-Flynn Declass - List of Unmaskings  https://www.hsgac.senate.gov/imo/media/doc/2020-05-13%20ODNI%20to%20CEG%20RHJ%20(Unmasking).pdf Declass - FBI Document that Launched CrossFire Hurricane  https://www.judicialwatch.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/JW-v-DOJ-reply-02743.pdf Declass - General Flynn / Kislyak Transcripts  https://www.grassley.senate.gov/sites/default/files/2020-05-29%20ODNI%20to%20CEG%20RHJ%20%28Flynn%20Transcripts%29.pdf,"[{u'text': u'Hilary Clinton - Insurance', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'MLK - Assassination Committee', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'One', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'FISA Infographic', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'https://img.theepochtimes.com/assets/uploads/2018/03/22/fisa-spying-infographic.jpg', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'China War on America Infographic  ', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'Zero', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Just The News John Solomon - Russia Collusion Hoax  https://justthenews.com/accountability/political-ethics/key-witness-told-team-mueller-russia-collusion-evidence-foundnMockingbird Media  https://centipedenation.com/analysis-and-reports/operation-mockingbird-a-social-engineered-reality/', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'4/16/20', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'FISA Abuse Timeline: Epoch  https://cdn.epoch.cloud/assets/static_assets/FISA-abuse-timeline.jpgnDeclass - Planned Parenthood', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'George Floyd Protests  https://centipedenation.com/transmissions/massive-dump-of-video-clips-documenting-looters-and-violent-riots-during-george-floyd-protests/', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Eric Trump', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'53', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Susan Rice E', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Michael Flynn  ', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Flynn / Kislyak Transcripts', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",37
6664660,"NOTIZIA IMPORTANTISSIMA CHE  DOVETE FARE GIRARE ASSOLUTAMENTE E ANCHE  ALLA SVELTA.   IN QUESTI GIORNI GLI OPERATORI TELEFONICI A PARTIRE DA VODAFONE (IL CUI AMMINISTRATORE DELEGATO VODAFONE ITALIA È GUARDATE CASO VITTORIO COLAO, L'UOMO LEGATO ALLA COMMISSIONE TRILATERALE E AL CLUB BILDERBERG, QUINDI POTERI OCCULTI,See more MA SOPRATTUTTO L'UOMO MESSO A CAPO DELLA TASK FORCE PER LA 5G,  PERSONAGGIO A CAPO DI STRUTTURE CON CONFLITTI D'INTERESSE PESANTISSIMI), CHE VI INIZIERANNO A PRENDERE D'ASSALTO CON I VARI CALL CENTER PER PROPORVI UN NUOVO CONTRATTO, CHE PREVEDERÀ IL DIMEZZAMENTO DEI COSTI A PATTO CHE ACCETTIATE DI PASSARE DALLA VOSTRA ATTUALE 4G ALLA 5G.  BOICOTTATELA FINO ALLA MORTE, PERCHÈ ATTRAVERSO QUESTO SISTEMA DI COERCISIONE=CONVINCIMENTO COMMERCIALE CHE FA LEVA SUI COSTI DEI SERVIZI INTERNET CI FOTTERANNO DEFINITIVAMENTE CON LA 5G, PERCHÈ SE ALMENO LA METÀ DELLA POPOLAZIONE LA ACCETTERÀ LORO AVRANNO LA FORZA DI INTRODURLA DEFINITIVAMENTE SENZA NEMMENO IL NOSTRO CONSENSO, CHE GLI ABBIAMO GIÀ TOLTO E CHE GRAZIE AL NOSTRO TAM TAM SOCIAL E WEB SIAMO RIUSCITI A BLOCCARLA, PORTANDO MOLTISSIMI SINDACI D'ITALIA E PAESI DEL MONDO A BLOCCARNE LA MESSA IN FUNZIONE DEFINITIVA.    FATE GIRARE!!!!! CONDIVIDETELO SUI PROFILI DEI VOSTRI AMICI!!!! METTIAMO IN GUARDIA TUTTI DA QUESTA TRAPPOLA, E' IMPORTANTE!!! CI SI GIOCA IL NOSTRO FUTURO E MOLTI DI VOI ANCORA NON LO SANNO!!!","[{u'text': u'QUESTI GIORNI GLI', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'VITTORIO COLAO', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'AL CLUB BILDERBERG', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'CON CONFLITTI', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'CHE VI', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'CON', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'CHE PREVEDERxc0 IL DIMEZZAMENTO DEI', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'4', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'LA', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'NEMMENO IL NOSTRO CONSENSO', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'CHE GLI', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'GIxc0 TOLTO E', u'type': u'PRODUCT'}, {u'text': u'CONDIVIDETELO', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'METTIAMO', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",22055
6757909,Jenny whitehouse 9/10/22: “marked people”? Referring to vaccinated? Marked for the 5G death beams…?   @DismantlingTheCabal,"[{u'text': u'Jenny', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'9/10/22', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",37
6758791,"Graphene oxide nanoparticles were introduced already in the flu vax back in 2019 so most of the elderly were poisoned by the time the whole plandemic started. Now do you know where the globalist did a 5G pilot scenario? Yep Wuhan and Italy... coincidence? Every single old people's home and every single hospital has big 5G antenas near them... coincidence?? Young and fit people has high levels of glutathione in their bodies that's why covid doesn't affect them.... coincidence?? Graphene is not just being introduced into your body by injection PCR test and mask have it as well...do you know some of the symptoms of graphene in your body? Bilateral pneumonia, lost of smell, lost of taste.... familiar? Coincidence?  Graphene oxide nanoparticles are slowly washed away by your own inmume system that's why they need reppited doses...vax over and over.... coincidence?  Remember they were saying don't drink alcohol after 52 days after taking the jab.... alcohol (ethinol) helps reducing the effects... bars and pubs  closed.... coincidence??....and can carry on and on and on!!","[{u'text': u'2019', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Yep Wuhan', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Italy', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Graphene', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'PCR', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Graphene', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'52 days', u'type': u'DATE'}]",37
10029493,⏰ DIESE TECHNIK MIT 5G IST DAS ENDE DER MENSCHHEIT ⏰ 👉 BOSTON DYNAMICS 👈 https://www.bostondynamics.com/spot 👉 WORST NIGHTMARE 👈 for Russian Military US Military advanced robot technology https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BRym2d9hB64,"[{u'text': u'BOSTON DYNAMICS U0001f448n', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Russian Military', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'US', u'type': u'GPE'}]",519
10033135,⚠️5G APOCALYPSE - THE EXTINCTION EVENT⚠️ ❗️DIE TOTALE VERNICHTUNG❗️ A full length documentary by Sacha Stone exposing the 5G existential threat to humanity in a way we never imagined possible! AUTOMATISCHE DEUTSCHE ÜBERSETZUNG ZUSCHALTBAR https://invidio.us/watch?v=ol3tAxnNccY https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ol3tAxnNccY @buergerinformative #5G #Waffensystem #DieTotaleVernichtung,"[{u'text': u'G APOCALYPSE - THE', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'u2757', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'TOTALE VERNICHTUNGu2757ufe0fnA', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Sacha Stone', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'DEUTSCHE xdcBERSETZUNG ZUSCHALTBAR', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'https://invidio.us/watch?v=ol3tAxnNccY', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'#5G #Waffensystem', u'type': u'MONEY'}, {u'text': u'DieTotaleVernichtung', u'type': u'DATE'}]",519
10037453,⏰ DIESE TECHNIK MIT 5G IST DAS ENDE DER MENSCHHEIT ⏰ 👉 BOSTON DYNAMICS 👈 https://www.bostondynamics.com/spot 👉 WORST NIGHTMARE 👈 for Russian Military US Military advanced robot technology https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BRym2d9hB64,"[{u'text': u'BOSTON DYNAMICS U0001f448n', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Russian Military', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'US', u'type': u'GPE'}]",519
10130246,"🚫 F💀CK  5G ! 🚫  It says ""SURRENDER 5G SKEPTICS!"" written in the sky! Who the HELL would do something like this?  Las Vegas JAN -7 - 2020","[{u'text': u'SURRENDER 5G SKEPTICS', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'Las Vegas', u'type': u'GPE'}]",487
10140816,CON IL 5G SARÀ POSSIBILE CONTROLLARE DA REMOTO QUELLO CHE INIETTIAMO,"[{u'text': u'CON IL', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",329
10159467,🇪🇦 SPAIN – Barcelona: pigeons fall like stones from the sky ... it happens near the 5G antennas.,"[{u'text': u'SPAIN', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Barcelona', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",550
10563485,"Frank Clegg, ehemaliger Präsident von Microsoft Canada, heute CEO von Canadians for Safe Technology über 5G  https://youtu.be/eUoZf4xfbM4","[{u'text': u'Frank Clegg', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Prxe4sident von Microsoft Canada', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'von Canadians', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",3128
10934479,"#HelloWorld  The Storm Is Here!  Here is Film SEVEN of The Great Awakening Series known as Collab Storm Is Here! This is the film to share around! A Collection Of Information and Perceptions from a United Kingdom / United States of America perspective.  🎬 Film ONE: https://www.bitchute.com/video/sVJMTjeojNSY/ 📥 Download: www.t.me/TheGreatAwakeningCollabs  🎬 Film TWO: https://www.bitchute.com/video/5SPCWNEen3pm/ 📥 Download: www.t.me/TheGreatAwakeningCollabs  🎬 Film THREE: https://www.bitchute.com/video/I8DrGpvs2Qmg/ 📥 Download: www.t.me/TheGreatAwakeningCollabs  🎬 Film FOUR: https://www.bitchute.com/video/VT0FCbQtZ31P/ 📥 Download: www.t.me/TheGreatAwakeningCollabs  🎬 Film FIVE: https://www.bitchute.com/video/oovXdnx7EDDc/ 📥 Download: www.t.me/TheGreatAwakeningCollabs  🎬 Film MAJESTIC: https://www.bitchute.com/video/zzXtzLXmBV4C/ 📥 Download: www.t.me/TheGreatAwakeningCollabs  🎬 Film STORMISHERE: https://www.bitchute.com/video/azVnNCZFdpzH/ 📥 Download: www.t.me/TheGreatAwakeningCollabs  Description of The Great Awakening Film Collabs and the Content Within:  The Great Awakening Film Collab ONE - Q Anon - Trump - The Plan - E.U. Dictatorship - Perception - Anonymous - The System and The Earth - Google  The Great Awakening Film Collab TWO - JFK Jr - E.U. article 13 - Diversity - The E.U. - Soros - Monatch Programming / MK Uktra used in Christchurch shooting - The Great Replacement - Serialbrain2  The Great Awakening Film Collab THREE - Q Anon - MK Ultra / Monarch programming - Clown World - Yellow Vests Movement - Migrant / Immigrant invasion of Europe - Greece Migrant Invasion in Plain Sight - Satanism and Notre Dame Terror Attack - Facebook - Trump  The Great Awakening Film Collab FOUR - 9/11 - Sri Lanka Terror Attack - Notre Dame Attack - Robots - Immigration - Extinction Rebellion 💩 - 5G - Anonymous  The Great Awakening Film Collab FIVE - Q Anon - Nationalism Rising - White Genocide - Migrant Invasion - Venuzuela Coup - E.U. does not exist - Clinton Treason - Illuminati Plan - Blood Hungry (before ending) - UFO happening - Serialbrain2 - * Films now contain a glitch from one of the editing softwares causing 'Cyberlink' to appear during the last five seconds.  The Great Awakening Film Collab MAJESTIC - Q Anon - Deepstate - Secret Space Program  The Great Awakening Collab STORMISHERE - Q Anon Storm Special - Anonymous  All movies are designed to hack your perception into awakening mode  This is an anti-virus for your perception.  Please Share To Awaken Others. Credits To Original Creators.  This is a collaboration of The Great Awakening events currently ongoing, plus other parts to help open your perception.  The collection of clips is orchestrated as a film piece which can allow users to download and share.  We do not care for likes. Please share. Please post.  🕴️ ill see you Anon 🕴️ 🕴️🕴️ Expect Us 🕴️🕴️  Non-Profit. No Copyright. © Free.  #QAnon #Anonymous #WWG1WGA #Brexit #WW3 #NWO #Freedom #Freespeech #StormIsHere  * Please Note: The Great Awakening Series Is Designed As A Guide To Connecting Dots. There Is So Much Happening Worldwide We Cannot Include Everything In Our Series. We Also Ask You To Confirm With Your Own Research. *  - WE NEED YOUR HELP! - To share any suggestions for the collabs or even feedback please visit us here: https://t.me/TGACollabDropBox  - PLEASE SHARE, THANQ","[{u'text': u'The Storm Is Here', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'Series', u'type': u'EVENT'}, {u'text': u'Collection Of Information', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'United Kingdom', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'United States of America', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'ONE', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Download', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'TWO', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Download', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'THREE', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Download', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'FOUR', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Download', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'FIVE', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Download', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Download', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Download', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Content', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'The Great Awakening Film Collab', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'ONE', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Earth', u'type': u'LOC'}, {u'text': u'TWO', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'article 13', u'type': u'LAW'}, {u'text': u'E.U.', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Christchurch', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'THREE', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Europe', u'type': u'LOC'}, {u'text': u'Plain', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Notre Dame Terror Attack', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'FIVE', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'one', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'the last five seconds', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'The Great Awakening Film Collab MAJESTICn- Q Anonn- Deepstate', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'Original Creators', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Anon U0001f574ufe0fn', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'U0001f574', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'U0001f574', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Us U0001f574', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'U0001f574', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'xa9 Free', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'#QAnon', u'type': u'MONEY'}, {u'text': u'#Brexit', u'type': u'MONEY'}, {u'text': u'#NWO #', u'type': u'MONEY'}, {u'text': u'THANQ', u'type': u'ORG'}]",673
10937915,"NEW DOCUMENTARY PROMO   https://youtu.be/4Jq8t1wYY8Q  Watch the corruption at Gateshead council how bad they want to cover the 5G crime up. This council needs a serious looking into.  Mark Steele and Lee Garrett have been working so hard at outing the corruption and placing there lives on the line to speak out. They have had threats from councils and police, false arrests, mental health acts brought on them, social services for the children, false threats of life read out by Northumbria Police as scare tactics, threat of eviction and so on. Mark has had many court cases and Gateshead council have spent a significant amount of tax payers money to try and gag Mark, unfortunately the law courts can see through the lies and will not place a full gagging order on weapons expert Mark Steele for speaking out about his concerns on humanity with backed up research to prove he is correct.  Please share this video with your friends and family this is a must watch!!  Let's come together and put a stop to 5G!  Saving humanity together!    DO NOT IGNORE WATCH AND SHARE THIS VIDEO THIS PROVES HIW SERIOUS THIS IS!!!  ACT NOW!!!","[{u'text': u'Gateshead', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Mark Steele', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Lee Garrett', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Northumbria Police', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Mark', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Gateshead', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Mark', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Mark Steele', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",673
10950868,2019-07-15_ 5G Show_ Lee Garrett _ Mark Steele,"[{u'text': u'2019-07-15', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Lee Garrett', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Mark Steele', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",673
10950869,2019-07-22_ 5G Show_ Lee Garrett _ Mark Steele,"[{u'text': u'2019-07-22', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Lee Garrett', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Mark Steele', u'type': u'PERSON'}]",673
10964101,If 5G brings me closer to a PlayStation 9 I’m all for it https://youtu.be/IyPQVsdCuRk,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'PlayStation 9', u'type': u'PRODUCT'}]",672
10964662,"MORONS!!! 🇮🇱 Israel: Protest currently at Rabin Square in Tel Aviv against 5G  It should be noted that Israel does not have 5G, but does have over 10,000 coronavirus cases.","[{u'text': u'U0001f1ee', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Israel', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Rabin Square', u'type': u'FAC'}, {u'text': u'Tel Aviv', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Israel', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'10,000', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",672
10966876,Cell Phone RADIATION & 5G DANGERS - An In-Depth Exploration,[],673
10966891,"One of the 5G arsonists has been caught on camera.  This is the radio tower at the Koningsweg in Groningen.  My man just drove up in broad daylight and went for it, lol.","[{u'text': u'One', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Koningsweg', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Groningen', u'type': u'GPE'}]",876
10968635,"During the week, 53 5G network masts were attacked in the UK. https://www.businessinsider.com/attacks-cellphone-towers-coronavirus-5g-conspiracy-2020-4  British mobile operator EE said conspiracy theorists pose a “risk to human life” by setting fire to telecommunications masts. During Easter weekend alone, 22 EE telephone masts were burned. https://inews.co.uk/news/coronavirus-lockdown-latest-5g-conspiracy-theories-ee-phone-masts-easter-2538429  The attack also damaged the Vodafone mast, serving the Chelmsley wood hospital in Birmingham. https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/11400110/5g-coronavirus-conspiracy-theory-arson-attack-nightingale-hospital-vodafone-birmingham/  Homes in Huddersfield were also evacuated early on Tuesday morning after a mast attached to the Fearnleys Mill home development was set on fire, destroying equipment belonging to three network providers.  Another mast in Birmingham, which provided mobile connectivity to the city's recently-erected Nightingale Hospital, was also attacked over the weekend.  The vast majority of the phone masts were not carrying 5G equipment, meaning 2G, 3G and 4G network infrastructure essential to emergency services  during the outbreak was affected.","[{u'text': u'the week', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'53 5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'UK', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'British', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'Easter weekend', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'22', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Vodafone', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Chelmsley', u'type': u'LOC'}, {u'text': u'Birmingham', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Huddersfield', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Tuesday', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'morning', u'type': u'TIME'}, {u'text': u'Fearnleys Mill', u'type': u'PRODUCT'}, {u'text': u'three', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Birmingham', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Nightingale Hospital', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'the weekend', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'2', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'3', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'4', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",672
10975890,"Few days ago, the world's tallest 5G tower was installed on Mount Everest using yaks to transport equipment.","[{u'text': u'Few days ago', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Mount Everest', u'type': u'LOC'}]",672
10977203,https://t.me/DoomsdayDisclosure 5G / Gates Foundation / Go 😜 Wild,"[{u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'G / Gates Foundation', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U0001f61c', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",672
10977594,https://t.me/DoomsdayDisclosure Invite anyone into 5G / Gates Foundation / Fringe / UFO / Off-World / Hyperdimensionals,"[{u'text': u'Invite', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'G / Gates Foundation / Fringe / UFO / Off-World / Hyperdimensionals', u'type': u'ORG'}]",672
10978147,"🇬🇧 Police have arrested 14 people for breaching lockdown restrictions after they took part in a protest opposing lockdown in London today.   During the demonstration at St James Park, they promoted conspiracy theories about coronavirus, relating to 5G and vaccinations.","[{u'text': u'U0001f1e7 Police', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'14', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'London', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'today', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'St James Park', u'type': u'FAC'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",672
10982193,The public in shock! Bird death in Croatia after installing and operating the 5G tower two days ago. Everyone worries about what's going on out there!  It was tested on the frequency 7.40 GHz.  Citizens send photos from all places! It's no coincidence! Why are they silent about this? STOP 5G.  The fire trees 5 G masts are in the United States. Example of how you're covering the 5G masts. Source FB :Geikler Friedrich Maik,"[{u'text': u'Bird', u'type': u'PRODUCT'}, {u'text': u'Croatia', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'two days ago', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'7.40', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'the United States', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",672
10985948,Bird mortality in Croatia after installing and switching on the 5G tower 2 days ago. Everyone is worried about what happens! It has been tested on the frequency of 7.40 GHz. Citizens send pictures of all the places! Why are they silent about it?,"[{u'text': u'Bird', u'type': u'PRODUCT'}, {u'text': u'Croatia', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'2 days ago', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'7.40', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",672
11020604,Soviel zu 5G  @Into_the_Light_News,"[{u'text': u'Soviel', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}]",4040
11052762,"Working toward a more resilient microelectronics supply chain, while also addressing national security risks:   ""We can no longer clearly identify the pedigree of our microelectronics,"" which are key to technologies like 5G as well as components in many weapons systems, Ellen Lord said. ""Therefore, we can no longer ensure that backdoors, malicious code or data exfiltration commands aren't embedded in our code.""  The United States is one of three countries that has microelectronics manufacturing capabilities, but according to a 2016 report from the Congressional Research Service, American microelectronics manufacturers have increasingly moved microchip fabrication plants abroad.  https://www.upi.com/Defense-News/2020/08/20/Pentagon-Its-time-to-bring-microelectronics-manufacturing-to-US/4331597965789/","[{u'text': u'Ellen Lord', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'The United States', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'one', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'three', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'2016', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'the Congressional Research Service', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'American', u'type': u'NORP'}]",672
11053211,"36. Concern grows about shortage of plasma after FDA expands access to COVID-19 treatment. The FDA issued an emergency use authorization for convalescent plasma.  37. For the first time in three decades, military families and retirees are getting revamped IDs. The card will be more durable and more closely resemble the Common Access Cards.  38. Pentagon: It's time to bring microelectronics manufacturing to U.S. The U.S. government must entice companies to do more microelectronics manufacturing in the United States, the Pentagon's undersecretary for acquisition and sustainment said Thursday. Working toward a more resilient microelectronics supply chain, while also addressing national security risks: ""We can no longer clearly identify the pedigree of our microelectronics,"" which are key to technologies like 5G as well as components in many weapons systems, Ellen Lord said. ""Therefore, we can no longer ensure that backdoors, malicious code or data exfiltration commands aren't embedded in our code."" The United States is one of three countries that has microelectronics manufacturing capabilities, but according to a 2016 report from the Congressional Research Service, American microelectronics manufacturers have increasingly moved microchip fabrication plants abroad.  39. The Department of Energy and Microsoft said they were partnering to create AI tools for disaster response. The DOE has created the First Five Consortium, which refers to the critical importance of how first responders make decisions in the first five minutes after a disaster strikes. Microsoft and the DOE, along with the Pacific Northwest National Laboratory and the Pentagon’s Joint AI Center, will apply AI tools to: ⁃Wildfire prediction and fire line containment (which is especially timely at the moment) ⁃Damage assessment  ⁃Search and rescue  ⁃Natural disasters ","[{u'text': u'36', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'FDA', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'FDA', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'37', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'first', u'type': u'ORDINAL'}, {u'text': u'three decades', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'the Common Access Cards', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'38', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Pentagon', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U.S.', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'U.S.', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'the United States', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Pentagon', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Thursday', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Ellen Lord', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'The United States', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'one', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'three', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'2016', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'the Congressional Research Service', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'American', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'39', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'The Department of Energy', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Microsoft', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'AI', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'DOE', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'the First Five Consortium', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'first', u'type': u'ORDINAL'}, {u'text': u'the first five minutes', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Microsoft', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'DOE', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'the Pacific Northwest National Laboratory', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Pentagon', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Joint AI Center', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'AI', u'type': u'GPE'}]",672
11054979,"""The true measure of something’s worth is the hours it takes to acquire it."" - Peter Diamandis  ""I’m more excited about the convergence of exponential technologies rather than any single tech. It’s the combination of AI + Robotics + VR + etc. that will yield new business models and transform industries. If I had to pick one, of course it would be Artificial Intelligence. It is hard for me to believe that anything else will be more impactful this next decade. But I’m a tech junky, so I get thrilled by the idea of combining 5G+VR/AR+AI… as well as AI + Genomics/CRISPR… this next decade is going to be quite a ride!"" - Peter Diamandis","[{u'text': u'u2019m', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'AI + Robotics + VR', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Artificial Intelligence', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'this next decade', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'u2019m', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5G+VR/AR+AI', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'AI + Genomics/CRISPR', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'this next decade', u'type': u'DATE'}]",672
11058904,"11. Small businesses have been constantly grappling with drastically reduced liquidity, disrupted supply chains, and lending challenges. To bounce back, they need to re-imagine their business models and identify their place and role in the new normal. Hence, most small businesses have realized that going digital is critical and now they are willing to disrupt them.   12. Russian national arrested for conspiracy to introduce malware into a Nevada company's computer network. Before attempting to flee the United States, the defendant allegedly plotted with co-conspirators to pay $1 million to a company employee to surreptitiously insert the malware. Kryuchkov graduated from St. Petersburg Polytechnic University, one of the world's leading universities in the training of programmers. The Tesla employee who refused to participate in the fraudulent operation was likely 31-year-old Ukrainian Dmitry Volkov.  13. Australia is grappling with a farm labor shortage just weeks from the start of the country’s winter grain harvest.  14. Chile salmon shortage sparks scramble for product. A national truck strike in Chile is affecting supply in the South American nation's main salmon market.  15. Since Friday, a series of earthquakes have occurred in Antarctica. One of them was a 5.1 on the Richter scale, said TN Colonel Emilio Obelar, head of the Uruguayan Artigas base.  16. The northern province of Jujuy is suffering an exponential increase in coronavirus cases, including among its top authorities, which has brought its health system to the brink of collapse. ""The situation is critical. We have 93 percent of the intensive therapy beds occupied by people from the hinterland of the province. In two or three weeks it will peak in San Salvador [de Jujuy, the provincial capital]. We are preparing for a collapse,"" said Sergio Barrera Ruiz, a doctor at Wenceslao Gallardo Hospital in Palpalá and a leading figure from the national medical association (AMRA, in its Spanish acronym). Last week, Marcelo Villa, the director of the Guillermo Paterson Hospital in San Pedro, the province’s second-largest city, said his hospital was on the verge of collapse.   17. Argentina makes moves to align with China over past 40 days. On July 7, the CEO of Huawei Argentina Steven Chen Shiqing met with the Chief of Staff of Chancellery for installation of technology with potential spy 5G, rejected by the Western world for threatening national security. On the same day, a convention was announced for the production of 9 million tons of pig meat, multiplying Argentine production 14 times. China renews the swap with the BCRA to strengthen its reserves. By August 7, in resolution 30917/20, the government authorizes the installation of the Chinese People's Army military base in Neuquén for satellite interception. On August 12, Argentina boycotts the presidency of the IDB for the USA. On the same day, the summit between the authorities of the JPs and the Chinese Communist Party increases international cooperation and exchange of political tables for their training.  18. Huawei focuses on cloud computing to secure its survival. Chinese company’s fast-growing unit still has access to US chips despite sanctions.  19. China is taking advantage of India’s intelligence failures. New Delhi has failed to learn from its mistakes.New Delhi and Beijing have now embarked on a fitful process of de-escalation. But even as the two parties seek to restore some semblance of normalcy along their shared border, a critical question lingers: Why was India’s security establishment seemingly blindsided by China? Local officials in Ladakh have in fact been sounding the alarm about Chinese forays into Indian territory for years, a fact that points to a complete breakdown in New Delhi’s intelligence gathering and risk assessment. It wouldn’t be the first time. And India doesn’t seem to be learning crucial lessons from previous security failures.","[{u'text': u'11', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'12', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Russian', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'Nevada', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'the United States', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'$1 million', u'type': u'MONEY'}, {u'text': u'Kryuchkov', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'St. Petersburg Polytechnic University', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Tesla', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'31-year-old', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Ukrainian Dmitry Volkov', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'13', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Australia', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'just weeks', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'14', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Chile', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'South American', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'15', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Friday', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Antarctica', u'type': u'LOC'}, {u'text': u'One', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'5.1', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'TN', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Emilio Obelar', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'16', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Jujuy', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'93 percent', u'type': u'PERCENT'}, {u'text': u'two or three weeks', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'San Salvador', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Sergio Barrera', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Wenceslao Gallardo Hospital', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Palpalxe1', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'the national medical association', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'AMRA', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Spanish', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'Last week', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Marcelo Villa', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'the Guillermo Paterson Hospital', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'San Pedro', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'second', u'type': u'ORDINAL'}, {u'text': u'17', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Argentina', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'past 40 days', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'July 7', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Argentina', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Steven Chen Shiqing', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'the same day', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'9 million tons', u'type': u'QUANTITY'}, {u'text': u'Argentine', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'14', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'August 7', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'resolution 30917/20', u'type': u'LAW'}, {u'text': u""the Chinese People's Army"", u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Neuquxe9n', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'August 12', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Argentina', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'IDB', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'USA', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'the same day', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'JPs', u'type': u'PRODUCT'}, {u'text': u'the Chinese Communist Party', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'18', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Huawei', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'US', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'19', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'India', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'New Delhi', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'New Delhi', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Beijing', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'two', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'India', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Ladakh', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'Indian', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'years', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'New Delhiu2019s', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'first', u'type': u'ORDINAL'}, {u'text': u'India', u'type': u'GPE'}]",672
11066616,"TRUMP UPDATED 25. August 2020  [- Trump Ukraine Impeachment Hoax](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/288)  [- Trump 88 - Mercury, Gemini and](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/706)        [9/11](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/4488)   [— BACKUP - Maybe I should do a new thread de](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/1136) [bunking Q - ""Deal of the Cen](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/1341)            [tury"" in the 33 room  - President Trump holds co](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/2123)       [ronavirus press confere](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/2132)         [nce   - Is Trump the Last President?  - TM Fi](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3201)  [lms - Trump CONFIRMS NYC CV Apocalyose](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3246)             [- President Trump: ""This was artifici](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3362)       [ally-induced  - Russianvids: Ivanka Trump Was Born A](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3370)      [Man  - Trump 2020 - Master Mason](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3429)      [s & Their Counter](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3456)         [feit Kingdom  - Trump Securing 5G 60GHz Death Grid](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3618)   [- ""I am the chosen one.""  - ThePottersC](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3666)           [lay - Exposing the Liars: Donald T](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3674)        [rump  - James True: The Role of Qanon in the T](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3698)       [rump Era  - TRUMP HAS](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3772)          [GIVEN THE REIGNS TO F.E.M.A.  - SMFP - Golden Gate Trump 8](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3779)      [8 OUTATIME Observation   - B](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/3856)            [lackpilled - HOPIUM CRISIS  - SMHP - Wil](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/4316)      [l We See A 2020 Presidential Election /](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/4394)         [Selection?  - COVID-19 is a live military](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/4413)      [exercise  - Article from 2012 (Trump,](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/4630)          [Fall of America)  - Trump](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/4783)       [seemingly sounds li](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/5063)     [ke he is saying ...  - ARM](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/5474)  [ED FORCES RESERVE](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/5560)       [S TO ACTIVATE ON US S](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/5735)  [OIL - The Unsettling Trump Predictive Pr](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/5756)   [ogramming  - Trump newer had a Flu shot !  - Operat](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/6280)        [ion Warp Sp](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/6360)            [eed  - Trump draining the swamp  - US cut ties with WH](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/6396)   [O  - Cambridge A](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/6421)            [nalytica  - Donald Trump Exposed:](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/6822)      [Zionist Front Man - Trump's New Icebreaker](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/6823)      [Fleet & Grand Solar Minimum 2020  - Facebook censor](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/6825)      [ship  - Trump &](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/7024)        [The Great Awakening: The Truth](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/7143)       [May Shock You   - Carlo Vigano open letter  - Tr](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/7158)  [ump officially wit](https://t.me/zuendels_bunker/3814)              hdraws from WHO  - BACK T[O THE FUTURE | 2016 ELECTION=T](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/7501)  [RUMP #88  - Donald Trump And The Circle Of](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/7624)    [Time (88, 9/11) - Busy  - Trump Wearing](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/7855)         [a Mask - Hoover Dam Pre](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8213)           [dicti](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8219)   ve[Programming  - Putin](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8232) [- BLM movement des](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8268)      [igned to dethro](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8495)   [ne Trump - Securingourinterests mirr](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8566)  [or many posts   NEW ADDITIONS - Matthew North videos](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8607)    [on PNAC  - Epstein, Maxwe](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8623)           [ll & Donald Trump Connections - Usin](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8638)     [g military to distribute COVID-](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8649)      [19 Vaccine - The Tale Of Two Trumps I](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8803)    [n 2020  - TikTok  - TikTok Microso](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8819)        [ft   - Operation Warp Speed  - Soro](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8883)               s on Trump  - ANONYMOUS: TRUMP-WORLD COMING DOWN  - The CV19 Mask Ritual - A Mass Mind Control Operation  - The Bidening | Trump Campaign Ad  - two roads to the same slaughter house  - Trump 2020 | The Last President ?  - Trump's Election Energy: 2016 vs 2020  - U.N. CONCERT OFFICIALLY ""DECLARES"" NWO  - Operation Trump - Successful As Planned","[{u'text': u'25', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'August 2020', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Gemini', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'BACKUP', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'de](https://t.me', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Cen](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/1341', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'33', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Trump', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'co](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/2123', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'confere](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/2132', u'type': u'PRODUCT'}, {u'text': u'Trump', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Donald T](https://t.me', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'8](https://t.me', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'8', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'2012', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'li](https://t.me', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'ED FORCES RESERVE](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/5560', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'US', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Flu', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'US', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Donald Trump Exposed:](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/6822', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Fleet & Grand Solar', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'2020', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'The Great Awakening', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'2016', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'T](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/7501', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'88', u'type': u'MONEY'}, {u'text': u'Donald Trump', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Time', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'88, 9/11', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'des](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8268', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'dethro](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8495', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Trump', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Matthew North videos](https://t.me', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Trump Connections', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'COVID-](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8649', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'19', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Vaccine', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'The Tale Of Two Trumps I](https://t.me/TheConspiracyHole/8803)   n[n 2020', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'Trump n- ANONYMOUS', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'TRUMP-WORLD COMING', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'2020', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'2016', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'2020', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'DECLARES', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'NWO', u'type': u'ORG'}]",4040
11066829,"Think about the power of THAT knowledge if you are assessing a hostile threat?! Changes your perspective a little, doesn’t it? From a camera perspective it gathers intel on vehicles in the area - yes, license plates, registrations, make and models - as well as ground based activity such as hot spots where there is social unrest. The eyes in the sky give ground based units advanced intel so they can better prepare. Now look at the military assets that have a hundred times that capability like the Raytheon Sentinel, the Beechcraft RC-12 Guardrail, the EO-5C 'Crazy Hawk' unmanned drone and even the super powerful E-8 Joint Stars to name just a few - all of these aircraft are designed to intercept electronic communications, imagery and ground movements. The hunter-gatherer aircraft are operated by military forces and other government agencies in roles such as intelligence gathering, battlefield surveillance, airspace surveillance, reconnaissance, border patrol and fishery protection as well as traffic monitoring, law enforcement and other similar activities. If you think the Cessna capability was impressive, these are like a Terminator version of the Cessna on steroids.  For example, we are talking about capabilities like a ground penetrating radar that has the ability to look for tunnel systems. Or looking into buildings and houses - yes, through walls, roofs, and all. These guys use technology that is both old and new - NOTHING can hide from them. With the new 5G, it is said they can watch you using the wifi signals. The cameras on-board have the ability to take a picture of the dimples on a golf ball from space - imagine that from just 30,000 feet - they can literally read the text messages on your phone while you are chilling by the pool - and that mole on your left shoulder, you should probably get that looked at by a doctor… No joke. This stuff is insanely cool. When it comes to the Club K missile system however, you can’t just do a broad sweep - you have to know where to look. Thus the problem. If they are looking in the right spot(s) with the right equipment, then they could determine that a sea container may have a heat signal or signature that requires a ground investigation. This is where you would see the helo’s come into play to get a confirmed visual and then boots on the ground to neutralize the threat if confirmed. This folks, is why Trump says - if he wanted to eliminate the ground threat in these cities, he could do it within a few hours. No joke. You mix this level of intel with a bunch of high speed dudes on the ground and it’s game over - quickly.","[{u'text': u'hundred', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'the Raytheon Sentinel', u'type': u'LOC'}, {u'text': u'the Beechcraft RC-12 Guardrail', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'E-8 Joint Stars', u'type': u'PRODUCT'}, {u'text': u'Cessna', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Terminator', u'type': u'WORK_OF_ART'}, {u'text': u'Cessna', u'type': u'PRODUCT'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'just 30,000 feet', u'type': u'QUANTITY'}, {u'text': u'Trump', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'a few hours', u'type': u'TIME'}]",672
11069386,"79. The American Security Institute recently released a report and launched a campaign, featuring a billboard in Times Square, to draw further attention to the extensive array of sectors the Chinese government and its partners have invested into. But, exactly how much does the nation own? China produces 97 percent of U.S. antibiotics and about 80 percent of active pharmaceutical ingredients used in American drugs, giving the Chinese Communist Party absolute control of potentially life-saving medicine. For example, Chinese pharmaceutical companies supply 70 percent of the world's acetaminophen, commonly used in Tylenol. In 2017, the United States imported $4.6 billion in agricultural goods from China, which is also responsible for much of the global supply of soy and pea proteins that are found in nutritional supplements and synthetic meats. A Chinese firm has also purchased Smithfield, the world's largest pork processor and hog producer. Smithfield said in a later statement pertaining to their ownership structure that they are ""a U.S. company that provides more than 40,000 American jobs and partners with thousands of American farmers. The company was founded in Smithfield, Virginia, in 1936 and was acquired by Hong Kong-based WH Group in 2013. WH Group is a publicly-traded company with shareholders around the world. Anyone anywhere can purchase shares of WH Group on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange. WH Group’s shareholders include many large U.S.-based financial institutions."" The Chinese government's theft of intellectual property has been an open secret for decades. More recently, U.S. authorities have discovered China is funding American university researchers, who don't always disclose those contributions. The manufacturing of smartphones and other household items is heavily reliant on China, which controls most of the rare earth minerals that make those items work. Additionally, China is seeking to build 5G networks in the United States and other Western countries, which could potentially feed personal information and sensitive data to the Chinese Communist Party. Chinese firms have bought AMC Entertainment, Legendary Entertainment, and other media companies. Control of 8,000-plus of American theater screens and other media platforms allows China to project ""soft power"" and block unflattering depictions of the Chinese government from being presented, both in terms of creative production and mass distribution. Citing the nonpartisan economic think-tank Paulson Institute, the American Security Institute report underscores that ""Chinese firms and investors own a controlling majority in nearly 2,400 U.S. companies."" These include: AMC Entertainment (entertainment), Cirrus Wind Energy (energy), Complete Genomics (health care), First International Oil (energy), G.E. Appliances (technology), IBM—P.C. division (technology), Legendary Entertainment Group (entertainment), Motorola Mobility (technology), Nexteer Automotive (automotive), Riot Games (entertainment), Smithfield Foods (food), Teledyne Continental Motors and Mattituck Services (aerospace), Terex Corp. (machinery), Triple H Coal (mining), Zonare Medical Systems (health care). ""Under China's Communist Party dictatorship, private companies are forced to bend to the government's will,"" the report states. ""A recently passed law in China requires companies to share data with Chinese communist spy agencies if requested. [U]nder Xi Jinping, the Communist party has returned to being the ultimate authority in business,"" writes The Guardian. And Human Rights Watch has written that China is an 'existential threat' to human rights."" And while the U.S. grants China permission to buy its companies, China does not allow U.S. companies to operate the same way on their soil. ""The first priority is to reclaim our critical supply chains so that we can become self-secure instead of reliant on the Chinese government,"" Will Coggin, managing director of the American Security Institute, told Fox News. The extent of Chinese investment in recent years has also raised red flags around U.S.","[{u'text': u'79', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'The American Security Institute', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Times Square', u'type': u'FAC'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'97 percent', u'type': u'PERCENT'}, {u'text': u'U.S.', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'about 80 percent', u'type': u'PERCENT'}, {u'text': u'American', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'the Chinese Communist Party', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'70 percent', u'type': u'PERCENT'}, {u'text': u'Tylenol', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'2017', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'the United States', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'$4.6 billion', u'type': u'MONEY'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'Smithfield', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Smithfield', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'U.S.', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'more than 40,000', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'American', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'thousands', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'American', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'Smithfield', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Virginia', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'1936', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'Hong Kong', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'WH Group', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'2013', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'WH Group', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'WH Group', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'the Hong Kong Stock Exchange', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'WH Groupu2019s', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'decades', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'U.S.', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'American', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'5', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'the United States', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Western', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'the Chinese Communist Party', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'AMC Entertainment', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Legendary Entertainment', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'8,000-plus', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'American', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'Paulson Institute', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'the American Security Institute', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'nearly 2,400', u'type': u'CARDINAL'}, {u'text': u'U.S.', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'AMC Entertainment', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Cirrus Wind Energy', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Complete Genomics', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'First International Oil', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'G.E. Appliances', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'IBM', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'P.C.', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Legendary Entertainment Group', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Motorola Mobility', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Nexteer Automotive', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Riot Games', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'Smithfield Foods', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Teledyne Continental Motors', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Mattituck Services', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Terex Corp.', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Triple H Coal', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Zonare Medical Systems', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Communist Party', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'U]nder Xi Jinping', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'the Communist party', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Guardian', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Human Rights Watch', u'type': u'PERSON'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'U.S.', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'China', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'U.S.', u'type': u'GPE'}, {u'text': u'first', u'type': u'ORDINAL'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'the American Security Institute', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Fox News', u'type': u'ORG'}, {u'text': u'Chinese', u'type': u'NORP'}, {u'text': u'recent years', u'type': u'DATE'}, {u'text': u'U.S.', u'type': u'GPE'}]",672
